[
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 38?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "37",
      "39",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 40 or 4?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 11 or 9?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "9",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 32 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "19",
      "14",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 3?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-8",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 17 or 17?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "12",
      "17",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 39 or 2?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "6",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "4",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 21 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "23",
      "21",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 46?",
    "options": [
      "91",
      "97",
      "92",
      "93"
    ],
    "answer": "92"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 22?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "21",
      "25",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "22",
      "20",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "37",
      "42",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 33 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "34",
      "29",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "22",
      "25",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-6",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 12 or 11?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 15 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-1",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "38",
      "41",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 49?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "50",
      "46",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 9?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "9",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 32?",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "69",
      "68",
      "64"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 44?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "83",
      "93",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 42?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "47",
      "40",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 6?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "5",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "-9",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 8?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "11",
      "2",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-13",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 33?",
    "options": [
      "67",
      "70",
      "66",
      "65"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 44 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 35?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "38",
      "36",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 26 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "33",
      "38",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 17?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "22",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 32?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "26",
      "31",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 3 or 11?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "7",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 11?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "15",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 17?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "18",
      "16",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 48?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "53",
      "49",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 34 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "33",
      "36",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 36?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "72",
      "74",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 15 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "26",
      "25",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 26?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "50",
      "53",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 22?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "21",
      "18",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 8 or 3?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 2?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "9",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 45 or 20?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "19",
      "20",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 39?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "38",
      "33",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "29",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 12 or 16?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "11",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 + 18?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "70",
      "67",
      "71"
    ],
    "answer": "67"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "8",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 36 or 18?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "37",
      "31",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 14?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-4",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 + 10?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "19",
      "26",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 32?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "37",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 20?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "36",
      "42",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 28?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "56",
      "57",
      "61"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 5?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "7",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 45?",
    "options": [
      "89",
      "90",
      "94",
      "92"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 47?",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "46",
      "43",
      "47"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "1",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 14?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 5 or 3?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "3",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 48?",
    "options": [
      "99",
      "92",
      "100",
      "96"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 2 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "14",
      "18",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "39",
      "38",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 49?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "50",
      "48",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "-1",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "52",
      "57",
      "54"
    ],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 30?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "31",
      "27",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 4?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "36",
      "37",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 30 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "28",
      "34",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 18?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "16",
      "20",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "40",
      "42",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 45 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "48",
      "41",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 47 or 7?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "7",
      "6",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 33 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "42",
      "44",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 33 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "31",
      "27",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "6",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "-1",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "-7",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 14?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "12",
      "10",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 1?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "0",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 26 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "22",
      "26",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "8",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 37?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "36",
      "41",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 35?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "34",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "-1",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 12 or 20?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "16",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "53",
      "57",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "53"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 35 or 8?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "33",
      "30",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "23",
      "26",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 19?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "18",
      "21",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 47?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "41",
      "50",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 28?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "25",
      "24",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 15?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 2?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "1",
      "-4",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 27?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "58",
      "54",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 26 or 1?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "1",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "32",
      "35",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 11 or 16?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "15",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 20?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "23",
      "21",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 32 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "44",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 8 or 5?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 9?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 + 5?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "45",
      "49",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "-1",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "-2",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "4",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 30?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "29",
      "28",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 24 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "29",
      "21",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 15 or 19?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "18",
      "15",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 38 + 20?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "57",
      "60",
      "58"
    ],
    "answer": "58"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 22?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "28",
      "20",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 17 or 12?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 17?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "-7",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "-9"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 41 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "41",
      "37",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "50",
      "45",
      "49"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 42?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "41",
      "38",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 9?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "10",
      "11",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "9",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "28",
      "27",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 5 or 12?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "9",
      "12",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 7 or 5?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "12",
      "2",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 9?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "20",
      "18",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 29?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "28",
      "29",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "22",
      "17",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 44?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "39",
      "40",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 + 16?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "33",
      "38",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 17?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "14",
      "11",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 1 or 8?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 19?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "16",
      "17",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 4 or 3?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "5",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 18?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "36",
      "37",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "24",
      "22",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 19?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "34",
      "35",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 10 or 19?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "23",
      "19",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "8",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 34?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "34",
      "35",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 29?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "30",
      "26",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 8 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "12",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 35 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "38",
      "39",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 3 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "1",
      "-1",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 36 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "31",
      "38",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 33?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "35",
      "38",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 2 or 16?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "16",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "20",
      "19",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 20?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "44",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 39?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "33",
      "38",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-4",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 46?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "44",
      "48",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 8?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "2",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "24",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 15?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "16",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 45?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "51",
      "48",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "5",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 48 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "10",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 34 or 19?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "16",
      "14",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 34?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "30",
      "29",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 26 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "8",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 44?",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "43",
      "50",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 29?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "33",
      "28",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 16?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "15",
      "20",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-9",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 21 or 9?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "16",
      "24",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 22 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "15",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "0",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 9?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "8",
      "14",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 24?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "51",
      "46",
      "47"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 4?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "9",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 12?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "16",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 35?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "33",
      "39",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "14",
      "16",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 40 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "52",
      "54",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 47?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "50",
      "47",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 26?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "28",
      "21",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 44?",
    "options": [
      "88",
      "83",
      "89",
      "93"
    ],
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 39 or 6?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "35",
      "39",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 45?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "39",
      "44",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 31?",
    "options": [
      "58",
      "64",
      "62",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 33 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "10",
      "5",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "7",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "-1",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "9",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 14?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "13",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 26?",
    "options": [
      "57",
      "54",
      "52",
      "47"
    ],
    "answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 39 or 8?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "34",
      "40",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 33?",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "66",
      "61",
      "71"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "2",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "0",
      "7",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 45 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "41",
      "40",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-2",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 - 14?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "0",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "24",
      "26",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "33",
      "29",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 26?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "24",
      "29",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 28?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "56",
      "57",
      "58"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 + 10?",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "53",
      "48",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 13 or 19?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 43?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "89",
      "82",
      "81"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 34?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "38",
      "40",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 41?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "44",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 22 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "22",
      "21",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 30?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "26",
      "25",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 22?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "47",
      "49",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "7",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-8",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 50?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "56",
      "54",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 3 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "6",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 39?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "36",
      "37",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 31 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "24",
      "29",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 5?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "7",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 19?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "16",
      "18",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 47 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "48",
      "45",
      "50"
    ],
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 + 16?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "33",
      "28",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 28?",
    "options": [
      "59",
      "58",
      "56",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 3?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "0",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 18 or 9?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "13",
      "18",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 38 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "19",
      "10",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 37?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "32",
      "36",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "9",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 25 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "22",
      "25",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 2?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "6",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 25 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "20",
      "25",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 43?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "44",
      "42",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 3?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 45?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "90",
      "92",
      "85"
    ],
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 17?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "16",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 31 or 5?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "31",
      "34",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 40 or 7?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "7",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 15?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "17",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 24 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "25",
      "20",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 16?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "30",
      "36",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "-2",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 7?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "13",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "7",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "-6",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 25?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "29",
      "24",
      "26"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 41 or 7?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "46",
      "39",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 33 or 8?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "2",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 26 or 4?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "-1",
      "2",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "-9",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "40",
      "34",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "3",
      "7",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 40 or 17?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "38",
      "36",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 46 or 11?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "11",
      "14",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "8",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 + 20?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "31",
      "32",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 50 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "48",
      "53",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "52"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 37 or 12?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "9",
      "7",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 9?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "13",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 22 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "22",
      "23",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "-3",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 43?",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "86",
      "88",
      "90"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 13?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "19",
      "12",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 27 or 16?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "11",
      "12",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "28",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 43?",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "83",
      "86",
      "91"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 29 or 8?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "13",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "14",
      "16",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "0",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 37 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "49",
      "44",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 14 or 19?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "14",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 12 or 10?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "13",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 20?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-10",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 49 or 5?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 48?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "49",
      "48",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 13?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "23",
      "29",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 43 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "32",
      "35",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "43",
      "46",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 26?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "22",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 4?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "8",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 - 14?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "22",
      "28",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "21",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 29?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "32",
      "26",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 46 - 17?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "34",
      "29",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "8",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "-9",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "-2",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 48?",
    "options": [
      "94",
      "100",
      "96",
      "98"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 16 or 4?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "16",
      "18",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 13?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "17",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 19?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "23",
      "24",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "17",
      "20",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 16?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 30 or 7?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "32",
      "33",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 12 or 2?",
    "options": [
      "-3",
      "1",
      "-2",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 11?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "19",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "-9",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "-9",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 - 20?",
    "options": [
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "-9"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 47 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "47",
      "48",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "43"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 24 or 17?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "16",
      "17",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 36?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "35",
      "40",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "20",
      "15",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "0",
      "7",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 30?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "56",
      "60",
      "64"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "12",
      "11",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 42?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "39",
      "46",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "Triangle",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 49 or 4?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "45",
      "49",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "-8",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "Square",
      "-3",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Circle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 22 or 16?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "22",
      "26",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 17?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "18",
      "14",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 48?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "46",
      "49",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 28?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "29",
      "26",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 42 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "18",
      "10",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 15?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "Triangle",
      "Square",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "8",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 - 17?",
    "options": [
      "-16",
      "Rectangle",
      "Triangle",
      "Square"
    ],
    "answer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 7?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "6",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is double of 35?",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "74",
      "69",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "8",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 19 or 3?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "-8",
      "Rectangle",
      "Circle",
      "Triangle"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is smaller: 25 or 13?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "17",
      "11",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "27",
      "21",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "-1",
      "Circle"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "3",
      "-1",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 1 or 14?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "15",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes before 35?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "34",
      "39",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "7",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is greater: 10 or 15?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "17",
      "19",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the value of 10 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number comes after 27?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "28",
      "24",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  }
]